<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<openerp>
    <data>

        <!-- User Story Difficulty -->
        <record id="usp_hard" model="user.story.difficulty">
            <field name="name">Not Apply</field>
            <field name="estimated">0</field>
            <field name="points">0</field>
            <field name="help">It is an acceptance criteria which represent a feature already done by The softwre, it is just informative Acceptance Criteria</field>
        </record>
        <record id="usd_low" model="user.story.difficulty">
            <field name="name">Low</field>
            <field name="estimated">2</field>
            <field name="points">1</field>
            <field name="help">This is a task that develop it and make the push is really easy, even considering that the testing time will not take too much time because it can be done in a set of parallel changes. i.e. Add a field without intelligence, including the view and so on. This kind of thing is used too when the acceptance criteria is solved with a configuration of 2 or 3 screens</field>
        </record>
        <record id="usp_medium" model="user.story.difficulty">
            <field name="name">Medium</field>
            <field name="estimated">8</field>
            <field name="points">2</field>
            <field name="help">It will take at least one day, to set, test and validate some details, Frequently this difficulty is used when is necesary some workflow changes and some conceptual improvements not too difficult.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="usp_hard" model="user.story.difficulty">
            <field name="name">Hard</field>
            <field name="estimated">24</field>
            <field name="points">4</field>
            <field name="help">In this case is frquently the time needed for reports which compute new thing, functional fields which validate external stuff generally this kind of tasks is when we compute things in an special way. And when the "process change" is involved, may be a workflow affecting some feature and so on. </field>
        </record>
        <record id="usp_sobig" model="user.story.difficulty">
            <field name="name">So Big that they need to be broken down more</field>
            <field name="estimated">24</field>
            <field name="points">8</field>
            <field name="help"> This acceptance criteria is wrong defined, some stuff are not clear and maybe it needs to be re-defined in a new user story or in several user stories. </field>
        </record>

        <!-- User Story Priority -->
        <record id="usp_urgent" model="user.story.priority">
            <field name="name">Urgent</field>
        </record>
        <record id="usp_priority" model="user.story.priority">
            <field name="name">Priority</field>
        </record>
        <record id="usp_secondary" model="user.story.priority">
            <field name="name">Secondary</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</openerp>
